Overriding: out_dir = out-shakespeare-baseline
Overriding: device = cuda
Overriding: num_samples = 3
Overriding: max_new_tokens = 500
number of parameters: 10.65M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...


Clown:
Strike with the sweet man set boast on.
Stirrange the hands are thee us all they came.

Second Citizen:
Hast thou to heavens, to thy heart and comfort
Which ever hair late this over-beauty?

CORIOLANUS:
We may not peace thee, come, you are not play you:
They were done, and well.

CORIOLANUS:
And you have Coriolanus.

First CiTizen:
Well have goes one
To kill thrust for their honour's fearful offices
Marry their corns; some strengther advance.

MENENIUS:
Why they say,
Here they come to th
---------------

Men person, marry, sir.

Second Conspirator:
See, masters, wherefore he shall be the wagon--

Third Citizen:
What's worth to cast the people.

CORIOLANUS:
Now to the city to the people's time:
He doth remember to the common grace of the vice
That worthy tongues beards against us weak of learn.

Second Citizen:
What are there?

CORIOLANUS:
Here comes a voice that makes him for us
To our fever submit is consorts being a countryman,
Become marriage him to the crown choice, would have come to him
An
---------------

Mercutio is well,
For I have no man will the very heart.

Second Murderer:
I have done, marry mine own leads till you have heard:
How far is the senate goes his father's a cause?

First Murderer:
I have bought to thee for in this man to-night;
Who is in this county's land, that humllbers there;
And credition'd to the trrm of his death shade love is come about
To do another not choose by despite thee.

Second Murderer:
And I never see thee worsemble for ever delay,
He is offended so all holy swee
---------------
