Overriding: out_dir = out-shakespeare-context
Overriding: device = cuda
Overriding: num_samples = 3
Overriding: max_new_tokens = 500
number of parameters: 10.65M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...


Clown:
So, who is here?

Clown:
Ay, my lord, I will desire to answer this foul army.

PAULINA:
Have you no more noble more
Than what to the heart and now in act it ends.

CAMILLO:
Give me the death of him.

WARWICK:
No day and little conveyant,
That she would leave the foot of the house
Whose causel of the hour Capitol with them
Where I have stood to the rest ward of their sun;
And he must not know them, and so doubt?

Provost:
Hark, by hand, and they are not in the cause.

CLAUDIO:
Ay, I can c
---------------

Men pardon, marry, she's head; and he comes to purge
But with ready that she hath not used me.

TYBALT:
I must not might be a kind to peace thou art.

BRUTUS:
We do pass the other peers so;
One that shore e'er as not come, she should have done,
The other chance bear the warlike cowards she follows.

KING RICHARD III:
Spare the city, if I should be brief,
That thy seven and this determined common peril.

GLOUCESTER:
Why then it were bold made to him, then being at home
Your tent for for the gates
---------------

Me runner.

MARIANA:
Where is the earth in this, I can die;
To do withal honourable seeming to the gates,
And in their sovereign care would be call'd again:
She hath refused the cause of the ancient comes!

COMINIUS:
Let him be witness.

DUCHESS OF YORK:
Save thou for Hereford, Tranio, spare me offence
Not a good word; Master Of Ely, and Grey are his;
The flower doth him quickly have been so much,
Cry to thy garments. And I never weep
Then at omic mercy should claim fins you out
But when let me 
---------------
